https://www.teachoverseas.ca/privacy.php

Post Your Teaching Job - Find Your Teacher Today!
HomeEFL Overseas TeachersPOST Your EFL ResumePOST Your EFL TutoringEFL Teaching JobsEFL Training CoursesEFL RecruitersEFL Teaching BlogEFL Teaching ForumEFL Information - Q&AEFL Teachers GuideEFL ResourcesEFL LessonsEFL Teacher ScamsEFL ClassifiedsEFL Overseas SchoolsPOST Your EFL Teaching JobPOST Your EFL Training CoursePOST Your EFL School InfoPOST Your EFL Recruiting ServiceEFL Teachers ResumesEFL Teaching BlogEFL Information - Q&AEFL ResourcesEFL LessonsEFL ClassifiedsEFL LinksEFL Overseas ResourcesEFL ResourcesEFL LessonsEFL Teaching BlogEFL Teachers GuideEFL Information - Q&AEFL Teacher ScamsEFL ClassifiedsEFL ArticlesEFL Overseas StudentsEFL SchoolsEFL TutorsEFL ResourcesEFL Teaching BlogEFL Information - Q&AEFL ArticlesEFL LinksEFL ClassifiedsEFL Overseas Jobs FeedsEFL Jobs Overseas Top JobsEFL Jobs Overseas OnlineEFL Jobs Overseas AsiaEFL Jobs Overseas SE AsiaEFL Jobs Overseas South KoreaEFL Jobs Overseas ChinaEFL Jobs Overseas TaiwanEFL Jobs Overseas JapanEFL Jobs Overseas ThailandEFL Jobs Overseas EuropeEFL Jobs Overseas Middle EastEFL Jobs Overseas Latin AmericaEFL Jobs Overseas South AmericaEFL Jobs Overseas Central AmericaEFL Jobs Overseas North AmericaEFL Jobs Overseas OceaniaEFL Jobs Overseas Africa
Post Your Teaching Job - Find Your Teacher Today!
Teach Overseas Privacy Policy
Home
Welcome to Teach Overseas, a site for English speaking teachers wanting to teach overseas. Teach Overseas has the latest EFL teaching jobs, great teacher training courses as well as teaching resources and ideas.
Teach Overseas is an EFL resource for EFL teachers and the EFL teaching community teaching overseas to share EFL resources and information. At Teach Overseas Canada, you can find the latest EFL information to help you in your English teaching career overseas!
This privacy policy sets out how TeachOverseas.ca uses and protects any information that you give TeachOverseas.ca when you use this website.
TeachOverseas.ca is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
TeachOverseas.ca may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 1, 2017.
What we collect for Registered Users (if any)
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
other relevant information (user type, avatar, postings made)
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our services.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for site research and improvement purposes. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We currently use GeoTrust Security Monitoring Services to scan and detect any security issues. Please note that Registered Users will have their contact information displayed in the Account section: Name, Email, Avatar, General Information/Bio provided by Users, Posts by Users.
Under no circumstances would TeachOverseas.ca ever contact you for personal financial information.
How we use cookies
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to admin@TeachOverseas.ca.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Enjoy the site, enjoy the submissions and enjoy your life. We will you the best as you teach English and travel the world. That's an amazing thing! Celebrate and investigate, collaborate and commiserate, laugh and cry, shake your head and wonder why. That's what Teach Overseas is all about.
Site Administrator will make the final decision on any and all information, posts, requests, etc. for posting on this site. Please read the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy regarding further information on the use of this site. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. You can learn more about Icon Education Group here.
Welcome to the wonderful world of EFL!
Featured Postings:
Post
job
Today!
Post
resume
Today!
Post
teacher
Today!
Post
tutor
Today!
Post
course
Today!
Post
resource
Today!
Post
school
Today!
Post
classified
Today!
Post
recruiter
Today!
Post
lesson
Today!
Post
information
Today!
Post
scam
Today!
Graduate your school to true tablet-driven education with Icon Educate Digital Learning Solution
